realtyaustin.com 2015-03-25

# Realty Austin Privacy Policy

## **Realty Austin's Privacy Policy**

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give certain information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact you about the listings and services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or when you register on the site. We will not share, sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to customer service requests, administer your account and send you newsletters. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information _only as necessary to provide_ these services to us or as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about services, new listings, market information or changes to this privacy policy.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at realtor@realtyaustin.com.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You can do the following at any time by contacting us at 512-241-1300, via email at realtor@realtyaustin.com or by logging into your account.

    •    See what data we have about you, if any.

    •    Change/correct or delete any data we have about you.

**Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it] by making the change on our member information page, by emailing our Customer Support at realtor@realtyaustin.com, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Tell-A-Friend**

If you choose to use our share this article to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Realty Austin does not store this information, which is only used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us.  We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

**Third Party Cookies**

The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is not covered by our privacy statement.  We do not have access or control over these cookies.  Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies [to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order to keep track of your home preferences, etc.]

**Web beacons**

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

**Customer Testimonials/Comments/Reviews**

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information.  We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

**Blogs**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Surveys & Contests**

From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at realtor@realtyaustin.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 512-241-1300 or via email at realtor@realtyaustin.com.

**Physical Address:**

3801 N. Capital of Texas Highway  
Suite J-180  
Austin, TX 78748
